mypeoplenet.com 2003-06-08

# PeopleNet® - a CIGNIFY network

Cignify.com Web Site Privacy Statement

Cignify believes that privacy is important to the success and use of the Internet.  This statement applies to **Cignify.com** and all other sites owned by Cignify (the "Sites") and describes the practices Cignify will follow with respect to the privacy of users, including Cignify's clients and employees, and including all information that is transmitted through the MyPeoplenet portion of this site ("MyPeopleNet").  Cignify may change this Privacy Statement from time to time.  Any users that provide their current e-mail address to Cignify through the Sites will be given notice regarding any material changes made to this Statement.  If a user has not provided current e-mail contact information to Cignify through one of the Sites, such user should check this Statement periodically for any changes.

What is personally identifiable information?

"Personally identifiable information" is information that could reasonably be expected to be used to determine the indentity of a user, a client or a clients' employee, such as names, addresses, e-mail addresses, user ID's, credit card numbers, or Social Security numbers.

How is personally identifiable information collected, used, and disclosed?

It is important to distinguish between information provided by users via the Sites information that is available about Cignify's clients, or Cignify's clients' employees through MyPeopleNet (wether such information was provided through a Site or through some other medium).

Collection, use, and disclosure of personally identifiable information on the Sites.

Cignify does not collect personally identifiable information from the Sites without asking for it.  Cignify may request that users voluntarily supply information, including e-mail addresses, street addresses, telephone numbers, or other information to enhance the user's visit to the Site or to follow up after a user's visit.  Whether or not such information is provided is entirely up to the user.

A user's voluntary provision of personally identifiable information serves as consent to the collection and use of such information as described in the relevant parts of this Privacy Statement.   In some circumstances, Cignify may share information it collects from the Sites with its trusted business partners.   Except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Statement, Cignify does not sell or rent personally identifiable information collected through the Sites to any third parties.   Cignify may provide aggregate statistics about users of the Sites, such as volume, traffic patterns, and related information to reputable third-party vendors, but these statistics will include no personally identifiable information.   Cignify may also disclose personally identifiable information in special cases when it has a good faith belief that such action is necessary to (a) conform to legal requirements or comply with a legal process, (b) protect and defend our rights or property, (c) enforce the Web Site Terms and Conditions of Use, or (d) protect the interests of users or others.

Collection, use, and disclosure of personally identifiable information at MyPeopleNet.

Personally identifiable information that is available about a specific individual who is employed by or similarly affiliated with a client of Cignify may be available at MyPeopleNet either because it was entered through the Sites or some other medium (e.g., by loading batch files to the network) for hosting by Cignify.   Such information is generally governed by the terms of a separate written agreement between the parties, and in the event of a conflict between such agreement and this Statement, the written agreement shall control.   Cignify may use such information only to fulfill its obligations under the written agreement.   Cignify offers password protection to its clients for use when discussing personally identifiable information on Cignify's 1-800 line and for MyPeopleNet at no additional charge.   Clients shall, in their sole discretion, elect to use or not to use such password protection.   Clients that elect not to use password protection waive any and all rights the client might otherwise have relating to a breach of security that occurred in whole in part, directly or indirectly, because of the Client's failure to use password protection.

**What are cookies and how are they used?**

The Sites, like other commercial web sites, may utilize a standard technology called "cookies" to collect information about how the Sites are used.   Cookies are small strings of text that web sites can send to a web browser.   Cookies were designed to help a web site operator determine that a particular user had visited the site previously and to save and remember any preferences that may have been set while the user was browsing the site.   Cookies cannot retrieve any other data from a hard drive or obtain an e-mail address.   If a user is simply browsing the Site(s), a cookie may be used to identify the user as one that has visited the Site(s) before.

Cignify may also make use of memory-based cookies to authenticate the user of certain Cignify web applications (for example, MyPeopleNet).  Similarly, if a user is a registered user of a Site that provides services to Cignify clients (and has a user ID and password), Cignify may use cookies so that it can provide personalized information based on indicated preferences.   Although a user has the ability to modify most browsers to either accept all cookies, notify the user when a cookie is sent, or reject all cookies, it may not be possible to utilize those Cignify services which require registration if cookies are rejected.

What are your choices regarding collection, use, and distribution of your information?

If a user has voluntarily provided information at the Site(s) (not including provision of information in MyPeopleNet), the user has consented to the collection and use of its personally identifiable information as described in this Privacy Statement.   If, in connection with a user's use of a particular service, Cignify asks to use data in a way not described in this Privacy Statement and a user does not wish to permit that use, the user can choose not to use the particular service.

If a user has voluntarily provided personally identifiable information at the Site(s) (not including provision of information in MyPeopleNet), Cignify may, from time to time, send mail or e-mail regarding products and services.  If a user does not want to receive such offers and mailings, that choice can be made by checking the appropriate box on the submission form.

How can you correct, access, and update your information?

A user may view and edit its personally identifiable information at any time by contacting us using the link provided on the Site.

How do we protect your personally identifiable information?

Cignify uses reasonable measures, consistent with those that are standard in Cignify's industry, to protect personally identifiable information from access by unauthorized persons.   This includes, among other things, standard techniques such as firewalls, encryption, intrusion detection, and site monitoring.   Cignify also uses reasonable internal controls, consistent with those that are standard in Cignify's industry, to protect personally identifiable information from misuse by Cignify's employees.   Unfortunately, no electronic data or transmission can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.   As a result, while Cignify uses reasonable measures to protect personally identifiable information, it cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information transmitted or otherwise provided to it or received from it.   This is especially true for information that is transmitted via e-mail that is unprotected until it reaches Cignify's servers.   Once a transmission is received, Cignify uses the reasonable measures set forth above to secure its servers.

Internally, Cignify restricts access to personally identifiable information to employees who need access to the information in order to do their jobs.  These employees are limited in number and are instructed to adhere to Cignify's privacy policies.

How can you help protect your information?

If a user is using a Site for which it registered and chose a password, Cignify recommends that the password not be divulged to anyone, except employees who have a need to know the password for the performance of their duties.  Cignify will never ask for a password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited e-mail.   Also, it is important that users sign off of the Site(s) and close their browser window when finished using the Site(s).  This is to ensure that third parties cannot access personal information and correspondence if they have access to the relevant computer.

Other sites

The Site(s) may contain links to other sites, including those of Cignify's business partners.   While Cignify seeks to link only to sites that share its standards and respect for privacy, it is not responsible for the privacy practices employed by other sites.  Users are encouraged to review the privacy policy of any site linked to from the Site.

Transfer of Business Assets

As we continue to develop our business, we may be acquired, merge with another business, or acquire or buy other businesses or assets.   In such transactions, user and client information, including information about clients' employees, generally are among the transferred business assets.   In such an event, both personally and non-personally identifiable Information will be one of the transferred assets.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should contact Matthew Tallman at [matthew.tallman@cignify.com](mailto:matthew.tallman@cignify.com)
